<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="help_list_ans">
       
        <item>
            Like to degust the wine?  Want to keep their impressions?  Then this is the app for you!
        Create your favorite wines database – WineDB,  take photo front and back wine labels, 
        add rating, scan wine code, add notes, share wines with friends via Twitter, Facebook 
        and Email, backup and restore wine data to and from your mobile device and PC</item>

        <item>
            Application stores the data of your WineDB in SqLite database format – 
        this is file winmemo.db3 in folder \\sdcard0\\WineMemo\\</item>

        <item>
            In first install application WineDB  contain initial set of entries for fill wine 
        cards – for wine types, grape varieties,  wineries, countries, vintage, % alcohol 
        and sugar. These dictionaries help you enter your wine quick and easy</item>

        <item>
            WineDB   save two images for each entry - front and back wine labels. 
        Thumbnail to display in list of records is automatically created from the first image</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu - Settings - Image Sizes.  Select the desired size 
        to save the image in WineDB. (Image size 960 x 1280 enough to read the label and scan 
        the code to the devices screen)</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu - Settings - Thumbnail Size.  Select the desired 
        size to save a thumbnail to display in the list of entries</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries,  press Menu - Settings - Background color images. Choose one of 
        three backgrounds for the substrate below the image when viewing or editing card wine</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries,  press Menu - Settings –Search.  You can switch the search only 
        by name, or by multiple keywords</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu - Search.  Enter the string in the search box. 
        As you enter a string in the list will show the records containing the value you typed. 
        To exit the search mode, press Back</item>

        <item>
             Go to the list of entries, press Menu - Sort.  In the list, select the field 
        by which you want to sort the list of wines </item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press + .  Enter data in wine card. You can fill in yourself or choose 
        from catalogs. Add your impressions and rating. Press OK  to save wine card</item>

        <item>
            In edit card mode drag the slider bar with arrows at the bottom of the screen up.  
        The image window will open. You can save two images for each wine card.  
        Swipe left to switch to view and edit second image, swipe right to view and edit 
        first image.  Tap to Image button to add first image in wine card, you can load 
        image from your picture gallery, or take a photo</item>

        <item>
             You can add scan-code to wine card –insert it from last scan value (button Insert) 
       or fill it manually (not the most convenient way to) </item>

        <item>
            To quick delete wine card - long tap on the item in list you want to delete. 
       To delete  wine card in view mode select Menu - Delete</item>

        <item>
             Short tap to position in list you want to edit. In view mode tap Edit button in top screen </item>

        <item>
            Make short tap to position in list to view wine card. Double tap to image (or zooming with your 
        fingers) to view enlarged image.  Repeated double tap – reset zoom.  You can view enlarged 
        image in edit wine card mode too</item>

        <item>
            You can add scan-code in wine card, or search wine in your WineDB by scan-code. 
        Tap Scanner button in list mode to find wine in your WineDB. You can use Google Search, 
        if the wine is not found in your WineDB.  Wine Memo store last scan-code value, 
        you can use it to add or create new wine card</item>

        <item>
            Make short tap to position in list to view wine card.  Tap Share button in top screen 
        to share your impressions with friends via Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, email</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu – Export and Import database (DB).  Select item Unload DB. 
        Set DB name to unload, confirm operation.  DB extension will be added automatic. 
        Application will save your WineDB in Download folder of your device</item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu – Export and Import database (DB).  Select item Load DB. 
        Select wine database in database list and press Select.  Then confirm the selection. 
        Application will load WineDB </item>

        <item>
             Go to the list of record, press Menu - Import record. The application allows you 
        to share record in the format WineMemo Event - file like WME_record_name.wmde. 
        You can send the record as an email attachment (see. Export events). The resulting 
        record can be downloaded in its database in several methods. The first way - 
        open a letter, and select View to attach. This will start the loader records 
        WineMemo, where you can see the full information about the record is 
        received and upload it. Next way - save the attachment to your Download folder. 
        Then, in view mode Download files to open the event (the file is opened loader 
        records WineMemo).  Other way - open the list of received records stored in the 
        folder Download, through the application menu. In this case, you enter the Import 
        records you will see a list of records for download. Select an record will be open 
        Event Viewer, from which you can add it to the database 
             </item>

        <item>
              In view mode tap Menu, then Export record button in menu list to export record in 
       WineMemo record format (wmde file) via mail client  
             </item>

        <item>
            Go to the list of entries, press Menu – Diagramm. Select attribute to
        built diagramm</item>

        <item>
            contact us by email – droidwelt@gmail.com</item>

        <item>
            ERP-system development, mobile applications development -  www.altamix.ru 
            </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>